Daniel Abad Noriega

Front-End Developer Jr | Full Stack Developer Jr | Metrological 2D/3D

Palencia, Castilla y León, España

Contact

611613079 (Mobile)
daniel.abad.noriega@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ danielabadnoriega (LinkedIn)

Core skills

Teamwork

Css3

Problem solving

Certifications

Web Development Part-Time
Bootcamp March-September 2021

Resume

I have been working in an industry sector as metrologist for more than 5 years. I love to evolve and be better professionally and i discovered Web Development. I discovered a new world of possibilities and creativity. This is very challenging and grateful for your own.

Because of that, almost 3 years i started to study Web Developer passionately in an Academy from Spain, Ilerna online. I was studying online while i was working in my full time job. I feel that i needed specialize more skills and i enrole to myself in IronHack web development while i was ending my studies of Ilerna. There, in IronHack, i evolved to a Full-Stack Developer and learn MERN stack technologies (MongoDB, Express, React, NodeJS).

I am very proud of this success in my way.

Currently, I'm working as a metrologist in Inmapa Aeronáutica S.L. but i'm very motivated to explore this new way. I'm eager to keep learning about web development and gonna be more expert!

¿My hobbies? I am a hearty traveler and a sport lover.

If you have any questions that I can help with, please feel free to reach out here on LinkedIn or or contact me directly at daniel.abad.noriega@gmail.com. I look forward to speaking with you!

Experience

ICON Multimedia

Web Developer Junior January 2022 - Present

My main responsibility consisted of the development with HTML5, CSS and Javascript and the resolution of the different compatibility problems of these objects with the native system of the company in different multimedia players.

Inmapa-Aeronautica S.L.

Quality officer (level 3) November 2016 - January 2022

In this job we verify that all machined parts finished from millings machines and lathes applying CATIA V6, three-dimensional machine for measuring and various measuring devices for measure two dimensions of all finished machined parts. We verify the compliance with requirements of all pieces of final customer.

ACIARIUM S.L.

Officer level 5 June 2016 - November 2016

In this enterprise, I thrilled and machined metal parts for ships applying aluminium and stainless steel as main material. I use FANUC and HEIDENHAIN as mechanical programs.

TELESTANT SERVICIOS SL

Jazztel's Call Center Agent June 2011 - February 2014

As a call agent I was marketing ADSL, mobile lines and smartphones from JAZZTEL's company calling and be called by phone to all customers from

Education

ILERNA FP Online

Technician in Web Application Development, Computer Programming *October 2019 - November 2021*

Ironhack

Web Development Part Time Bootcamp

March-September 2021

I.E.S. Trinidad Arroyo

Technician in Manufacturing Production Programming Mechanics, Machining Technician \cdot (2013 - 2016)